[{"question":"which object is smaller?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The concrete cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The marble cube"}],"answer":1},{"question":"What is the material of the large cube?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"Redunknown"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"Bamboo"}],"answer":0},{"question":"How many cubes there?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"3"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"4"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Which object has larger density?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The large concrete cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The large plastic cube"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Is the large plastic cube lighter than the large concrete cube?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Which object has larger friction?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The large plastic cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The large concrete cube"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Which object has lower restitution?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The large redunknown cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The large concrete cube"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Which quadrant will the large RedUnknown cube be in when it finally stops moving ?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"\u2160"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"\u2161"},{"choice_id":2,"choice":"\u2162"},{"choice_id":3,"choice":"\u2163"}],"answer":2},{"question":"Which quadrant will the large concrete cube be in when it finally stops moving ?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"\u2160"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"\u2161"},{"choice_id":2,"choice":"\u2162"},{"choice_id":3,"choice":"\u2163"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Which object will stop moving earlier?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The large redunknown cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The large plastic cube"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Which object will stop moving first?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The medium marble cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The large concrete cube"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Will the medium marble cube travel to quadrant \u2160?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Will there a collision in the quadrant \u2163?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":1},{"question":"How many collisions will happen between objects?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"<=3"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":">3"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Will the large concrete cube collide more than once?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Will the large plastic cube collide with the large concrete cube in this video?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Will the large plastic cube collide with the large RedUnknown cube in this video?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Which objects is the first collision?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The large concrete cube and the wall"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The large plastic cube and the large concrete cube"},{"choice_id":2,"choice":"The large redunknown cube and the large concrete cube"},{"choice_id":3,"choice":"The wall and the medium marble cube"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Which objects is the last collision?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The large concrete cube and the wall"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The wall and the large plastic cube"},{"choice_id":2,"choice":"The large plastic cube and the large concrete cube"},{"choice_id":3,"choice":"The medium marble cube and the large plastic cube"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Will the medium marble cube collide with other objects after it stops moving?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":0}]